[
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VENUGOPALA P S's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VENUGOPALA P S's email is venugopalaps@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ANKITHA K's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ANKITHA K's email is ankitha.praj@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRAJWAL HEGDE N's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRAJWAL HEGDE N's email is prajwal.hegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ANKITHA SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANKITHA SHETTY's email is anki.shetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MURALI S IYER's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MURALI S IYER's email is muralis.iyer@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHARADA U SHENOY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHARADA U SHENOY's email is sharadauday@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SUDESH RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SUDESH RAO's email is sudesh.rao@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. DISHA D N's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. DISHA D N's email is disha.dn@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MAHESH B L's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MAHESH B L's email is mahesh.bl@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SWATHI PAI M's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SWATHI PAI M's email is swathi.pai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SNEHA SHETTY R's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SNEHA SHETTY R's email is sneha.r@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SMITHA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SMITHA's email is smitha.rai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. RAKSHITHA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. RAKSHITHA's email is rakshitha.s@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ANIRUDHAN ADUKKATHAYAR C's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ANIRUDHAN ADUKKATHAYAR C's email is anirudhan.c@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr.  ARUN M KUDUR's email?",
        "answer": "Mr.  ARUN M KUDUR's email is not listed."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. UJWAL P's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. UJWAL P's email is ujwal.p@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VIDYA S M's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VIDYA S M's email is drvidyasm@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. CHETAN D M's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. CHETAN D M's email is chetan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHYAMA PRASAD SAJANKILA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHYAMA PRASAD SAJANKILA's email is shyama.sajankila@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ANIL KUMAR H S's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ANIL KUMAR H S's email is anilkumar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VINAYAKA B SHET's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VINAYAKA B SHET's email is vinayakabshet@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SANTHOSH POOJARY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SANTHOSH POOJARY's email is santhoshnellikatte@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VENKATESH KAMATH H's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VENKATESH KAMATH H's email is venkatesh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SANDESH K.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SANDESH K.'s email is sandeshk@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ULLAL HARSHINI DEVI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ULLAL HARSHINI DEVI's email is ullalharshini@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SNEHA NAYAK's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SNEHA NAYAK's email is snehanayak@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. LOUELLA CONCEPTA GOVEAS.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. LOUELLA CONCEPTA GOVEAS.'s email is goveas.louella@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. HARSHITHA M JATHANNA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. HARSHITHA M JATHANNA's email is harshithaj@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. I RAMESH MITHANTHAYA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. I RAMESH MITHANTHAYA's email is viceprincipal.nmamit@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. A N PARAMESWARAN's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. A N PARAMESWARAN's email is director.iic@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ARUN KUMAR BHAT's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ARUN KUMAR BHAT's email is arun.bhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SRINATH SHETTY K's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SRINATH SHETTY K's email is shettysrinath@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. BHANDAGE A. R's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. BHANDAGE A. R's email is not listed."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. BHOJARAJA B E's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. BHOJARAJA B E's email is be.bhojaraj@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RANJITH A's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RANJITH A's email is ranjith.anand@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHAIK KABEER AHMED's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHAIK KABEER AHMED's email is kabeer@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHRIRAM MARATHE's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHRIRAM MARATHE's email is shrirammarathe@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is M. LOKESH J K's email?",
        "answer": "M. LOKESH J K's email is lokeshjk@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. PUSHPARAJ's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. PUSHPARAJ's email is pushparajmanai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MITHUN B M's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MITHUN B M's email is mithunbm@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHANMUKHA SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHANMUKHA SHETTY's email is shettyshanmukha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr.SUNDIP SHENOY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr.SUNDIP SHENOY's email is sundipshenoy@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. GURURAJ ACHARYA's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. GURURAJ ACHARYA's email is rajnitte@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAKSHITH KUMAR SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAKSHITH KUMAR SHETTY's email is rakshithshetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ROSHAN RAI's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ROSHAN RAI's email is roshanrai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MANJUNATH M's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MANJUNATH M's email is manjum@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ARJUN K PUNJA's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ARJUN K PUNJA's email is not listed."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. THUSHAR SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. THUSHAR SHETTY's email is shettythushar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRASHANTH KUMAR K's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRASHANTH KUMAR K's email is prashanthanitte@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRITHVIRAJ H K's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRITHVIRAJ H K's email is prithvirajhk@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRADEEP KARANTH's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRADEEP KARANTH's email is pradeepkaranth@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. THANUSHREE A HEGDE's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. THANUSHREE A HEGDE's email is hegdethanu@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. DEEKSHITHA K's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEKSHITHA K's email is deekshitha.k@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RADHAKRISHNA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RADHAKRISHNA's email is radhakrishna@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ASHISH SINGH's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHISH SINGH's email is ashishsingh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. CHITHRA K's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. CHITHRA K's email is chithra.k@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SHRINIVASA's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SHRINIVASA's email is shrinivasa.naik@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MANJUNATHA A S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MANJUNATHA A S's email is manjunatha.as@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. KRISHNA PRASAD D S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNA PRASAD D S's email is krishnaprasad.cc@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SANDEEP KUMAR S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SANDEEP KUMAR S's email is sandeep.kumar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. CHIDANANDA T's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. CHIDANANDA T's email is chidananda.t@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. MAMATHA  K M's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. MAMATHA  K M's email is mamatha.km@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NIRANJAN N. CHIPLUNKAR's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NIRANJAN N. CHIPLUNKAR's email is principal_nmamit@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. JYOTHI SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. JYOTHI SHETTY's email is jyothi_shetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. D K SREEKANTHA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. D K SREEKANTHA's email is sreekantha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VENKATRAMANA BHAT P's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VENKATRAMANA BHAT P's email is pv.bhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ARAVIND C V's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ARAVIND C V's email is Aravinda.cv@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SARIKA HEGDE's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SARIKA HEGDE's email is sarika.hegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr.SUDEEPA K B's email?",
        "answer": "Dr.SUDEEPA K B's email is udeepa@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAJU K's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RAJU K's email is rajuk@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr.  ANISHA P RODRIGUES's email?",
        "answer": "Dr.  ANISHA P RODRIGUES's email is anishapr@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. PALLAVI K N's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. PALLAVI K N's email is pallavi@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SANNIDHAN M S's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SANNIDHAN M S's email is sannidhan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SANDEEP KUMAR HEGDE's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SANDEEP KUMAR HEGDE's email is sandeephegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHABARI SHEDTHI B's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHABARI SHEDTHI B's email is shabarishetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAGHUNANDAN K R's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RAGHUNANDAN K R's email is raghunandan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAJALAXMI HEGDE's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RAJALAXMI HEGDE's email is rajalaxmihegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. PRADEEP KANCHAN's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. PRADEEP KANCHAN's email is pradeepkanchan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VIJAYA MURARI T's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VIJAYA MURARI T's email is vijayamurari.t@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. GANESH PAI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. GANESH PAI's email is ganesh.pai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KEERTHANA B CHIGATERI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KEERTHANA B CHIGATERI's email is keertahanabc@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. GURU PRASAD's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. GURU PRASAD's email is g.prasad@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHASHANK SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHASHANK SHETTY's email is shashankshetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. MINU P ABRAHAM.'s email?",
        "answer": "Ms. MINU P ABRAHAM.'s email is minupjuly12@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SAMPATH KINI's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SAMPATH KINI's email is sampath@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ASMITA POOJARY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASMITA POOJARY's email is asmitapoojari@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PAWAN HEGDE's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PAWAN HEGDE's email is pwnhegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SHWETHA G K's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SHWETHA G K's email is gk.shwetha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SAVITHA SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SAVITHA SHETTY's email is shettysavi1@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PUNEETH R P's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PUNEETH R P's email is Puneeth.rp@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. MANASA G R's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. MANASA G R's email is manasagr@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SUNIL KUMAR AITHAL S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SUNIL KUMAR AITHAL S's email is sunilaithal@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ANKITHA A NAYAK's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANKITHA A NAYAK's email is ankitha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mrs. SHILPA KAREGOUDAR's email?",
        "answer": "Mrs. SHILPA KAREGOUDAR's email is shilpamk@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ASHWIN SHENOY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ASHWIN SHENOY's email is ashwin.shenoy@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mrs. SOWMYA P's email?",
        "answer": "Mrs. SOWMYA P's email is sowmya.p@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. AKHILRAJ V GADAGKAR's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. AKHILRAJ V GADAGKAR's email is akhilraj.gadagkar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. JAYAPADMINI KANCHAN's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. JAYAPADMINI KANCHAN's email is jaya.padmini@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRITHVIRAJ JAIN's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRITHVIRAJ JAIN's email is prithvi.jain@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. RAJASHREE's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. RAJASHREE's email is rajashree@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. JOYLIN PRIYA PINTO's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. JOYLIN PRIYA PINTO's email is joylinpriya@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ANUSHA ANCHAN's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA ANCHAN's email is anusha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms.AISHWARYA. D. SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Ms.AISHWARYA. D. SHETTY's email is aishwarya.shetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mrs. SOUMYA ASHWATH's email?",
        "answer": "Mrs. SOUMYA ASHWATH's email is soumya.ashwath@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. VAISHALI BANGERA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. VAISHALI BANGERA's email is vaishali.bangera@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ROSHAN FERNANDES's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ROSHAN FERNANDES's email is roshan_nmamit@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SURYANARAYANA K's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SURYANARAYANA K's email is suryanarayana@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NAGESH PRABHU's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGESH PRABHU's email is prabhunagesh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. M SATYENDRA KUMAR SHET's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. M SATYENDRA KUMAR SHET's email is Satyendra@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAJALAXMI SAMAGA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RAJALAXMI SAMAGA's email is raji.samaga@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NAYANA SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAYANA SHETTY's email is nayanashetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ANITHA MARINA COLACO's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ANITHA MARINA COLACO's email is anithamp81@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. K. LATHA SHENOY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. K. LATHA SHENOY's email is lathashenoy@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. GIRISHA JOSHI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. GIRISHA JOSHI's email is girishjoshi85@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. NAVEEN J's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. NAVEEN J's email is naveenchikmaglur@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRADEEP KUMAR's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRADEEP KUMAR's email is pradeep@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. DINESH SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. DINESH SHETTY's email is dinesh1383@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr.  KRISHNA RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Dr.  KRISHNA RAO's email is not listed."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. DHANANJAYA B's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. DHANANJAYA B's email is Dhananjay.b@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. N S S RAMAKRISHNA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. N S S RAMAKRISHNA's email is ramakrishna.n@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MAHABALESHWARA SHARMA K's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MAHABALESHWARA SHARMA K's email is mahabaleshwara@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. RAKSHA ADAPPA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. RAKSHA ADAPPA's email is raksha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAVIKIRAN RAO M's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAVIKIRAN RAO M's email is ravikiranraom@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. GURURAJ K's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. GURURAJ K's email is raos2k@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MD ABDUL RAHEMAN's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MD ABDUL RAHEMAN's email is mararkeri@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SWATHI HATWAR H's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SWATHI HATWAR H's email is hswathihatwar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ANAND BHAT B's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ANAND BHAT B's email is anand.bhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SWATHI K's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SWATHI K's email is swathi.k@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. PALIMARU APARNA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. PALIMARU APARNA's email is palimaruaparna@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms.NUTANA SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Ms.NUTANA SHETTY's email is nutanakshetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ANUP SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ANUP SHETTY's email is anup.shetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. K RAJESH SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. K RAJESH SHETTY's email is krshetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. REKHA BHANDARKAR's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. REKHA BHANDARKAR's email is rekhabhandarkar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. K V S S S S SAIRAM's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. K V S S S S SAIRAM's email is drsairam@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VEENA DEVI SHASTRIMATH V.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VEENA DEVI SHASTRIMATH V.'s email is veenadevi@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. PRABHA NIRANJAN's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. PRABHA NIRANJAN's email is prabhan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. K S SHIVAPRAKASHA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. K S SHIVAPRAKASHA's email is shivaprakasha.ks@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KRISHNANAND SHET's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KRISHNANAND SHET's email is konikrishna@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SUBRAMANYA BHAT's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUBRAMANYA BHAT's email is sbhat22@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHANKAR B B's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHANKAR B B's email is shankarbb@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VIDYA KUDVA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VIDYA KUDVA's email is vidyakudva@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. DURGA PRASAD's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. DURGA PRASAD's email is durgaprasad@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ROOPA B HEGDE's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ROOPA B HEGDE's email is roopabhegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SUKESH RAO M's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUKESH RAO M's email is sukesh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MAMATHA GIRISH's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MAMATHA GIRISH's email is mamatha.girish@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHRIVIDYA G's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHRIVIDYA G's email is shrividyagp@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. PADMAVATHI K's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. PADMAVATHI K's email is padmavathik@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SUSHMA P S's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUSHMA P S's email is pssushma@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MAHAVEERA K's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MAHAVEERA K's email is mahaveera _nmamit@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SUNITHA LASRADO's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SUNITHA LASRADO's email is sunithadsouza@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SATHEESH RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SATHEESH RAO's email is Satheesh.rao@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NARENDRA K C's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NARENDRA K C's email is narendra@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHIVAKUMAR B R's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHIVAKUMAR B R's email is shivkumarbr@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ANUSHA R SHARATH's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ANUSHA R SHARATH's email is anushar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. BOMMEGOWDA K B's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOMMEGOWDA K B's email is bgowda_kbl@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KAVITHA S's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KAVITHA S's email is kavitha@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAVINDRA K S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAVINDRA K S's email is ravindraks@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRADYUMNA G R's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRADYUMNA G R's email is pradyumna@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. CHARISHMA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. CHARISHMA's email is shettycharishma@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. NIJU RAJAN's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. NIJU RAJAN's email is nijurajan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SHUBHA B.'s email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SHUBHA B.'s email is shubhab@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ANIL KUMAR BHAT.'s email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ANIL KUMAR BHAT.'s email is anilkumarbhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SUDARSHANA's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SUDARSHANA's email is sudarshan.rao@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. DILEEP KUMAR M J's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. DILEEP KUMAR M J's email is dileepmj@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms.NAGAPRIYA KAMATH's email?",
        "answer": "Ms.NAGAPRIYA KAMATH's email is nagapriyakamath@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. KARTHIK's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. KARTHIK's email is karthikamin@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. LAVANYA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. LAVANYA's email is lavanya.bl@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. DEEPA K's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEPA K's email is k.deepa7@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ANUPAMA B's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUPAMA B's email is anupamaece@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. RAMYA SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. RAMYA SHETTY's email is ramyahegdep@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ASHWINI K's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ASHWINI K's email is ashwinik@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. SHANKARI N.'s email?",
        "answer": "Ms. SHANKARI N.'s email is shankarimn@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. HARSHITHA BHAT.'s email?",
        "answer": "Ms. HARSHITHA BHAT.'s email is harshithabhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ASHWINI B's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHWINI B's email is ashwinib@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's email is balasubramani.r@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's email is karunapandit@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s email is karthikpai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VASUDEVA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VASUDEVA's email is Vasudeva.acharya@nitte-edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAVI B's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RAVI B's email is ravib671@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's email is ushad@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO's email is dr.manjulagururajh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr.SUMATHI PAWAR's email?",
        "answer": "Dr.SUMATHI PAWAR's email is drsumathi@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY's email is naganna.chetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's email is jason1987martis@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH's email is sunilkamath@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MANJUNATHA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA's email is manjunatha.msh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. DEVIDAS's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. DEVIDAS's email is devidasbhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. VASUDEVA PAI's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI's email is paivasudeva@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. DEEPA's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEPA's email is deepashetty17@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's email is rashmin@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's email is abhishekrao@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VAIKUNTH PAI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VAIKUNTH PAI's email is vaikunth.pai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's email is chinmai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SRIKANTH BHAT K.'s email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SRIKANTH BHAT K.'s email is srikanthbhatk@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's email is alaka_ananth@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SANTHOSH S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SANTHOSH S's email is santhosh.s@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's email is preethi.salian@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's email is krishnaraj.rao@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. PRATHYAKSHINI's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. PRATHYAKSHINI's email is prathyakshini@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. PRATHEEKSHA HEGDE N's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. PRATHEEKSHA HEGDE N's email is pratheeksha.hegde@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ANUSHA N's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N's email is anusha24@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. TANZILA NARGIS's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. TANZILA NARGIS's email is tanzilanargis@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. ASHWITHA C THOMAS's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. ASHWITHA C THOMAS's email is ashwitha.thomas@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SHRINIVASA RAO B.R.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SHRINIVASA RAO B.R.'s email is coe.nmamit@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SUBRAHMANYA BHAT K.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUBRAHMANYA BHAT K.'s email is subrahmanyabhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SUDESH BEKAL's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUDESH BEKAL's email is sudeshbekal@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SRINIVASA PAI P.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SRINIVASA PAI P.'s email is srinivasapai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NARASIMHA MARAKALA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NARASIMHA MARAKALA's email is nmarakala@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MALLIKAPPA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MALLIKAPPA's email is drmallikappa@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NARASIMHA K. BAILKERI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NARASIMHA K. BAILKERI's email is nkbailkeri@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. GURURAJ UPADHYAYA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. GURURAJ UPADHYAYA's email is gururaj@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. M. ANANTHA KRISHNA SOMAYAJI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. M. ANANTHA KRISHNA SOMAYAJI's email is aksomayaji8@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. UDAYA D's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. UDAYA D's email is udaya_d@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KUMAR H. S.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KUMAR H. S.'s email is urkumar2006@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. AJIT M. HEBBALE's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. AJIT M. HEBBALE's email is ajith.hebbale@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VIJEESH V's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VIJEESH V's email is vijeeshv@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. NITHIN KUMAR's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. NITHIN KUMAR's email is nithinmech33@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. GRYNAL D'MELLO's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. GRYNAL D'MELLO's email is grynal@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SURESH SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SURESH SHETTY's email is shettysuresh09@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VIDYASAGAR SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VIDYASAGAR SHETTY's email is vidyasagarshetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAVISHANKAR BHAT S's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAVISHANKAR BHAT S's email is ravishankarbhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAVINDRA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RAVINDRA's email is ravindra@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. P. VENKATESH MURTHY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. P. VENKATESH MURTHY's email is pvenkateshmurthy@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. AUSTINE DINESH D'SOUZA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. AUSTINE DINESH D'SOUZA's email is austindinesh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. SANTHOSH G.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. SANTHOSH G.'s email is santhug099@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. H.S SHARATH CHANDRA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. H.S SHARATH CHANDRA's email is sharathchandrahs@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VISHWANATHA J. S.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VISHWANATHA J. S.'s email is vishwajs@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. DILIP KUMAR K.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. DILIP KUMAR K.'s email is dilk333@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. DIVIJESH PUNINCHATHAYA P.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. DIVIJESH PUNINCHATHAYA P.'s email is divijesh@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAJATH N. RAO's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAJATH N. RAO's email is rajathnrao@gmail.com."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KRISHNAPRASAD S's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. KRISHNAPRASAD S's email is kprao@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAVIKIRAN KAMATH B.'s email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAVIKIRAN KAMATH B.'s email is ravikiran@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SRINIVAS PRABHU M.'s email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SRINIVAS PRABHU M.'s email is srikles@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MANJUNATH MAIYA's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MANJUNATH MAIYA's email is manjunath.maiya@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. GAUTAMA HEBBAR A.'s email?",
        "answer": "Mr. GAUTAMA HEBBAR A.'s email is gouthamahebbar@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. BHASKARA P's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. BHASKARA P's email is bhaskarap@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. MOHAN POOJARI's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. MOHAN POOJARI's email is mohan@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. SUNIL KUMAR SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. SUNIL KUMAR SHETTY's email is sunilkumarshetty@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RAGHAVENDRA PAI K.'s email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RAGHAVENDRA PAI K.'s email is pai7raghu@gmail.com."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MELWYN RAJESH CASTELINO's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MELWYN RAJESH CASTELINO's email is melwyn@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. MURALIDHARA's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. MURALIDHARA's email is drmuralidhara@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. VEERESHA R. K.'s email?",
        "answer": "Dr. VEERESHA R. K.'s email is veereshark@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RASHMI P SHETTY's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. RASHMI P SHETTY's email is iprashmi@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. ADARSH RAI's email?",
        "answer": "Dr. ADARSH RAI's email is adarsh.rai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. RANJITH BHAT's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. RANJITH BHAT's email is ranjith,bhat@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. RAJASHREE NAMBIAR P's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. RAJASHREE NAMBIAR P's email is rajashree.n@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. VINCENT LINISH DSOUZA's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. VINCENT LINISH DSOUZA's email is vincentldsouza@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ms. PRATHIKSHA PAI's email?",
        "answer": "Ms. PRATHIKSHA PAI's email is prathiksha.pai@nitte.edu.in."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mr. PRASAD PRABHU's email?",
        "answer": "Mr. PRASAD PRABHU's email is prasadprabhu@nitte.edu.in."
    }
]
